[Plot Love II]
[مؤامرة الحب الثاني]
[Episode 14]
[الحلقة 14]
Good morning, Mr. Lu.
صباح الخير سيد لو.
Good morning.
صباح الخير.
Mr. Lu greeted me.
السيد لو استقبلني.
Indeed.
في الواقع.
Mr. Lu.
السيد.  شمس.
The gang last night was caught by the police.
تم القبض على العصابة الليلة الماضية من قبل الشرطة.
Did they reveal the mastermind behind it?
هل كشفوا عن العقل المدبر وراءها؟
No.
رقم.
They insisted it was a drunken riot.
أصروا على أنها كانت أعمال شغب في حالة سكر.
Try to dig it out.
حاول أن تستخرجها.
Their target was Su Bei.
كان هدفهم Su Bei.
I'm afraid she will be in danger in the future.
أخشى أنها ستكون في خطر في المستقبل.
Okay.
تمام.
Ye Ting reported to the model department.
أبلغت يي تينغ قسم النماذج.
Got it.
فهمتك.
You are
أنت
a little different today.
اليوم مختلف قليلا.
Hum.
همم.
Am I?
هل انا
Anything good happened?
أي شيء جيد حدث؟
Gao Jiming, buy a bunch of roses
جاو جيمينغ ، اشترِ باقة من الورود
and send it to Su Bei's house.
وأرسلها إلى منزل Su Bei.
Well.
نحن سوف.
And a card,
وبطاقة ،
on which you should write...
التي يجب أن تكتب عليها ...
Ms. Su.
آنسة.  مع.
Flowers from Mr. Lu.
زهور من السيد لو.
- Who? - Mr. Lu.
- من؟  - السيد لو.
Bei, see you in the evening.
باي ، أراك في المساء.
Loving, Mr. Lu.
محبة ، السيد لو.
Lu Nan.
لو نان.
You came to me yourself.
أتيت إليّ بنفسك.
Bei.
في.
Why are you so active today?
لماذا أنت نشيط جدا اليوم؟
Why is it you?
لماذا انت
Mr. Lu, this is my home.
السيد لو ، هذا هو بيتي.
Where is Su Bei?
أين سو باي؟
You shouldn't ask me
لا يجب أن تسألني
about this.
عن هذا.
Su Manni, tell me
أخبرني عن ماني
where Su Bei is.
أين Su Bei.
Su Bei moved away.
ابتعد Su Bei.
Su Manni, watch your identity.
سو ماني ، انتبهي إلى هويتك.
I am your brother-in-law.
أنا صهرك.
Mr. Lu, don't worry.
السيد لو ، لا تقلق.
I won't tell my sister.
لن أخبر أختي.
Lu Nan.
لو نان.
I don't believe you don't like me at all.
لا أصدق أنك لا تحبني على الإطلاق.
I don't like you at all.
أنا لا أحبك على الإطلاق.
The person I like has always been your sister.
الشخص الذي أحبه كان أختك دائمًا.
What am I inferior to her?
ما أنا أدنى منها؟
I like you so much.
أحبك جداً جداً.
If the one from the Su family who's going to marry you was me,
إذا كنت أنا من عائلة سو الذي سيتزوجك ،
would you like me?
هل تحبني
Su Manni.
حول ماني.
I like Su Bei
أنا أحب Su Bei
not because she is the daughter of the Su family.
ليس لأنها ابنة عائلة سو.
Su Bei is Su Bei.
Su Bei هي Su Bei.
I have liked you
لقد أعجبت بك
since the first day I joined the company.
منذ اليوم الأول انضممت إلى الشركة.
I really wish you could give me a second look.
أتمنى حقًا أن تعطيني نظرة ثانية.
Su Manni...
عن ماني ...
Lu Nan.
لو نان.
I have worked so hard for so long
لقد عملت بجد لفترة طويلة
just to be closer to you,
فقط لأكون أقرب إليك ،
even a little bit.
ولو قليلا.
I finally got the chance to get engaged to you.
لقد أتيحت لي الفرصة أخيرًا للخطبة معك.
It was Su Bei who messed up.
كانت Su Bei هي التي أخطأت.
She stole what belonged to me.
لقد سرقت ما يخصني.
Why do you protect her so much?
لماذا تحميها كثيرا؟
Su Manni.
حول ماني.
You are just Su Bei's sister,
أنت أخت Su Bei فقط ،
not Su Bei.
ليس Su Bei.
I will never like you.
لن أحبك أبدا.
One more thing,
شيء اخر،
Su Bei is my fiancee.
سو باي هي خطيبتي.
We are getting along well.
نحن نسير على ما يرام.
If you dare
اذا كنت تجرؤ
to hurt Su Bei,
لإيذاء Su Bei ،
I will never let you go.
أنا لن اترك ابدا تغادر.
Bei.
في.
Where are you?
أين أنت؟
I'm at the company.
أنا في الشركة.
Why is Su Manni at your house?
لماذا Su Manni في منزلك؟
I have moved out from Su's house.
لقد خرجت من منزل سو.
I am coming for you.
أنا قادم لك.
Why are you here?
لماذا أنت هنا؟
Bei.
في.
What happened?
ماذا حدث؟
I returned the Su family's house.
عدت إلى منزل عائلة سو.
Why didn't you tell me?
لماذا لم تخبرني
I'm afraid you would worry about me.
أخشى أن تقلق علي.
Never mind.
لا تهتم.
I am already looking for a house.
أنا بالفعل أبحث عن منزل.
No need.
لا حاجة.
Live with me.
عش معي.
I just don't want you
أنا فقط لا أريدك
to worry about everything.
للقلق بشأن كل شيء.
I can fix it myself.
يمكنني إصلاحه بنفسي.
I know you can solve it.
أعلم أنه يمكنك حلها.
But you have me.
لكنك تملكني.
I don't want to make you work so hard.
لا أريد أن أجعلك تعمل بجد.
And we are a couple-to-be.
ونحن ثنائي المستقبل.
There is nothing wrong
لا يوجد شيء خاطئ
with us living together.
معنا نعيش معا.
Besides,
بجانب،
the gangster who attacked you at the BBQ stall before
العصابة التي هاجمتك في كشك الشواء من قبل
has not been found yet.
لم يتم العثور عليها بعد.
How could I not worry about
كيف لا تقلق
you living alone?
انت تعيش بمفردك
Are you moving or not?
هل تتحرك ام لا؟
All right.
حسنا.
I will.
أنا سوف.
I still want to kiss you.
ما زلت أريد تقبيلك.
Alright, finally finished.
حسنًا ، انتهى أخيرًا.
You've worked all day.
لقد عملت طوال اليوم.
Go to bed early.
اذهب الى السرير مبكرا.
You, too.
أنت أيضاً.
Okay.
تمام.
Good night.
طاب مساؤك.
Come in.
ادخل.
Bei.
في.
Is everything going on well?
هل كل شيء يسير على ما يرام؟
Yes.
نعم.
Well.
نحن سوف.
Go to bed early.
اذهب الى السرير مبكرا.
Okay, good night.
حسنًا ، ليلة سعيدة.
I am going back.
انا عائد.
Okay.
تمام.
Bei.
في.
Have some water.
اشرب بعض الماء.
If you're thirsty, you don't have to go downstairs.
إذا كنت عطشانًا ، فلا داعي للنزول إلى الطابق السفلي.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
Go to bed early.
اذهب الى السرير مبكرا.
Well...
نحن سوف...
Good night.
طاب مساؤك.
Okay.
تمام.
Bei.
في.
I got you a new pillow.
أحضرت لك وسادة جديدة.
Yours may not be comfortable.
قد لا تكون مريحة لك.
They are comfortable.
انهم مرتاحون.
Really?
هل حقا؟
Yes.
نعم.
Let me try.
دعني اجرب.
Lu Nan, what are you doing?
لو نان ، ماذا تفعل؟
It's really comfortable.
إنه مريح حقًا.
Get off.
انزل.
Go ahead.
إنطلق.
I am listening.
أنا أستمع.
Is the restaurant booked?
هل المطعم محجوز؟
Yes.
نعم.
♪Another♪
♪ آخر ♪
♪Long talk all night♪
♪ حديث طويل طوال الليل ♪
♪I haven't finished drinking the water on the table♪
لم أنتهي من شرب الماء على المائدة
♪I stare at the windowsill♪
أحدق في حافة النافذة
♪That fallen flower is no longer blooming♪
♪ تلك الزهرة الساقطة لم تعد تتفتح
♪You always say♪
♪ أنت دائما تقول ♪
♪Like and love♪
♪ اعجاب وحب ♪
♪Are similar but different♪
♪ متشابهة لكنها مختلفة ♪
♪Finally this time I'm being depended on too♪
♪ أخيرًا هذه المرة أنا أعتمد أيضًا
♪Listen and cover up, learn to sigh♪
♪ استمع وتستر وتعلم التنهد ♪
♪How happy you are laughing♪
♪ ما مدى سعادتك بالضحك
♪You are planning your future with her♪
♪ أنت تخططين لمستقبلك معها
♪I'm so numb, but I'm♪
♪ أنا مخدر جدًا ، لكنني ♪
♪Still listening♪
♪ ما زلت تستمع ♪
♪I don't have to guess your mind anymore♪
♪ ليس عليّ أن أخمن عقلك بعد الآن ♪
♪Is it funny, sad or helpless♪
♪ هل هو مضحك أم حزين أم عاجز ♪
♪Adults shouldn't lose their temper easily♪
♪ لا ينبغي أن يفقد البالغون أعصابهم بسهولة ♪